Periodicals Collection, 1784- (ongoing)
Sophia Smith Collection
- Alphabetical by title
  - L
    - LUA - Revista Feminista1981-82
    - Lucifer the Light Bearer1897-1907, [see Margaret Sanger Papers]
    - The Lucy Stone League Bulletin1954-70
    - Lunatic Fringe ("a newsletter for separatist, anarchist, and radical feminist lesbians in Chicago undated
  - M
    - Mademoiselle1935-38
    - Madras Birth Control Bulletin1932-38, [see Margaret Sanger Papers]
    - MNAD - A Women's Literary Journal1981-83
    - A Magazine of Appalachian Women1978
    - Mahjubah - The Magazine for Muslim Women1981-82
    - Maine Freewoman's Herald1975-76
    - Maine Women's Newsletters1974
    - Maize - A Lesbian Country Magazine1984-91
    - Majority Report1971-79
    - Makara, The Canadian Magazine by Women for People1975-78
    - Malaysian Medical Journal1936-37, [see Margaret Sanger Papers]
    - The Malthusian (title changed to The New Generation)1922-49, 1915-52, [see Margaret Sanger Papers]
    - Mama Bears News and Notes (Oakland, CA)1987-89
    - Mammy1972
    - Mana - Mexican American Women's National Association1978
    - MANA News (Midwives Alliance of North America)1983-
    - Manushi1979-80
    - Margins (special issue)1975
    - Marin County Women's News Journal1972-75
    - Margaret Sanger Papers Project Newsletter1991-
    - Marriage and Family Living (formerly Living)1941-52, [see Margaret Sanger Papers]
    - Marriage, Divorce, and the Family Newsletter1974-77
    - Marriage Hygiene1934-37, [see Margaret Sanger Papers]
    - Mary Wollstonecraft Journal1974, [see microfilm M16]
    - Mary Wollstonecraft Newsletter1972-73, [see microfilm M15]
    - La Maternite Heureuse1959-60, [see Margaret Sanger Papers]
    - Matriarchist, undated (circa early 1980s)
    - Matrices1977-81
    - Matrix: a Publication of Ultimate Womon1980
    - Matrix (New York City)1978
    - Mauve Messages1975, [see Homosexuality Collection]
    - McCall's1950-2001
    - Media Report to Women1972-88
    - Medical Woman's Journal1943, [see Margaret Sanger Papers]
    - La Medicina de Hoy (Cuba)1937-38, [see Margaret Sanger Papers]
    - ME, Jane1972
    - Metropolitan Gazette (Atlanta)1982
    - The Michigan Suffragist1914
    - Mitteilungen Des A.D.F.1931-33
    - MOMMA1972-74
    - Mom's Apple Pie: Lesbian Mothers' National Defense Fund Newsletter1975-78
    - Monadn'ock Woman, The1974
    - Monthly Cycle: a Newsletter by & for Lesbians1980
    - The Monthly Extract1972-78
    - Moonstorm: Lesbian Feminist Newsletter for Women1978-80
    - Mother1971
    - The Mother (The American Committee on Maternal Welfare)1941, [see Margaret Sanger Papers]
    - Mother & Child (National Council for Maternal and Child Welfare, London)1941, [see Margaret Sanger Papers]
    - Mother Demdike News1978
    - Mother Earth Bulletin1906-18, [see microfiche M33]
    - Mother Lode1971-72
    - Mother's Magazine and Family Circle1836-71
    - Motherhood Journal1979-85
    - Mother's Journal1862-75
    - Motive1972, [see Homosexuality Collection]
    - Mountain Laurel1990-91
    - Mountain Moving: a Feminist Quarterly1976-79
    - Le Mouvement Feministe1927-35
    - Mouvement Francais pour la Planning Familial1957-63
    - Moving Out - Feminist Literary and Arts Journal1971
    - Ms.1972-2008
    - Ms. On Scene Newsletter (became Studio Feminist Alliance)1973-75
    - Ms...Understood (YWCA-USC Women's Center Newsletter)1979
    - La Mujer (Columbia)1968-70
    - La Mujer (Mexico)1970
    - Mujer y Desarrollo (Dominican Republic)1978-82
    - La Mujer Feminista: Revista de la Union de Mujeres (Spain)1983-84
    - Mujer/Fempress (Chile)1993
    - Mujer Sociedad (Peru)1984-87
    - Mundo Femenino (Columbia)1956-57
  - N
    - NACW's Breakthrough, [see Breakthrough]
    - National Anti-Slavery Standard1840-70
    - National Association of Business Women Journal1976-79
    - National Association of Parents and Professionals for Safe Alternatives in Childbirth
    - (NAPSAC)1977-93
    - National Association for Physical Education of College Women Newsletter1964
    - National Business Woman1974-87
    - National Citizen and Ballot Box Index1976, [see also microfilm M22 for 1876-81]
    - National Life1929-31, [see Margaret Sanger Papers]
    - NCAN News - National Coalition of American Nuns1982-84
    - National Conference of Puerto Rican Women Newsletter1974
    - National Conference of Puerto Rican Women New York Chapter Newsletter1976-83
    - National Council f Women in India Bulletin1950-60
    - National Council of Women of the US Bulletin1902-84
    - National Council of Women - Woman Power in Action Newsletter1968-98
    - National Notes (National Association of Colored Women)1953-56
    - National NOW Times [previously Do It Now!]1975-2000
    - National Right to Life News1979-
    - National Woman's Party Bulletin1966-68
    - National Women's Political Caucus (Women's Political Times)1971-
    - National YWCA Bulletin 1951-1962
    - Needlecraft - The Home Arts Magazine1932-33
    - Network (Baltimore-Washington)1982-83
    - Network (Salt Lake City)1983-85
    - Die Neue Familie1950-66, [see Margaret Sanger Papers]
    - New Books on Women and Feminism1987-96
    - The New Broadside: A Female Exploration Sheet1970-82
    - The New Broom1970-71
    - The New Century for Women1876
    - The New Citizen1912-14
    - New Directions for Women1972-93
    - New Directions for Women in Delaware1975-79
    - New England Women's Studies News1976-80
    - New Era (Chicago)1885, [see Frances Casement Papers; microfilm M38]
    - The New Generation, [see The Malthusian]
    - The New Homemaking News (Korea)1947
    - New Lowell Offering1977
    - The New Northwest1871-87, [see microfilm]
    - The New Schools Exchange Newsletter1974
    - New Southern Citizen1914-16
    - New Woman1971-79
    - New Women/ New Church1978-95
    - New York Feminist Tribune1970
    - New York Woman1986-88
    - New Women's Times1975-84
    - New York Radical Feminists Newsletter1974-77
    - New York Suffrage Newsletter1901-10
    - 9 to 51972-84
    - No More Cages1980-84
    - No More Fun and Games1968-73
    - Nk Lapia (Hungary)1950-51, [see Countries Collection, box Gr-C]
    - The Northern Woman (Ontario)1974-78
    - NEPCA News - Newsletter for the Northeast Popular Culture/ American Culture Association May 2004
    - Notes (from the "First Year," "Second Year," and "Third Year") (New York RadicalWomen1968-71
    - Noticias de Mujeres (New Mexico Commission on the Status of Women)1977-83
    - NOW!1973-78
    - NOW Acts1968-73
    - NOW News (Boston)1974-77
    - NOW News (Los Angeles)1971-72
    - NOW Newsheet1974-76
    - NOW Times (Springfield, MA)1982-95
    - The NOW Times (Van Nuys, CA)1976-79
    - The NOW York Times1979
  - O
    - Off Our Backs1970-
    - On Our Backs1984-95
    - Ohio Woman1973-78
    - Ohoyo - A Bulletin for American Indian-Alaska Native Women1979-83
    - The Oklahoma New Woman1975-77
    - Old Maid1975, [see Homosexuality Collection]
    - Old Sleuth Library1886
    - On Campus With Women1972-86
    - On Our Way: The Women's Center Newsletter (Cambridge, MA)1971-78, [see Women's Liberation Collection]
    - On the Issues: The Progressive Women's Quarterly1984-94
    - The Open Door1930-37
    - The Operative Magazine1841
    - Oregon Council for Women's Equality197?
    - Die sterreicherin1936
    - The Other Woman (Toronto)1972-76
    - Our Herald1882-84, [see microfilm M38; Frances Casement Papers for 1884]
    - Our New Humanity1895-97
    - Our Own (Norfolk, VA)1988-89
    - Our Own (Older Women's Network, Inc, Wolf Creek, OR)1978-80
    - Our Paper - A Voice for Lesbians and Gay Men in Maine1985-86
    - Ours1978-80
    - Out in Comics, 2003, [see Homosexuality Collection]
    - Outcry - A Publication of the Task Force on Battered Women and Sojourner Truth House (Milwaukee)1977-79
    - Outlook: National Lesbian and Gay Quarterly 1988, [see Homosexuality Collection]
    - Outwrite Women's Newspaper1984
  - P
    - Paginas1951-54
    - Paid My Dues1974-80
    - Pandora (Seattle)1972-78
    - Pan Pacific and Southeast Asia Women's Association (PPSEAWA) Bulletin1959-66
    - Pax et Libertas1920-72
    - Pax International1937-50
    - Peace & Freedom, 2000-
    - Peace News1940
    - The Pearl Street Journal (Women's Services Center, Pittsfield, MA, formerly Women's Pearl)1979-80
    - Peking Review1958, [see Margaret Sanger Papers]
    - The Pedestal (Vancouver)1970-74
    - Peer Perspective1975-82
    - People: A Magazine for All the People1931, [see Margaret Sanger Papers]
    - People1980
    - The People's Press1970
    - Peterson's Magazine1846-88
    - The Pink Paper - The National Newspaper for Lesbians and Gay Men1991-96
    - Pioneer Woman (Women's Labor Zionist Organization of America)1980-84
    - Plainswoman1983-87
    - Planned Parenthood Bulletin (Family Planning Association of India)1953-96, [see Margaret Sanger Papers]
    - Planned Parenthood Federation of America, Inc. News Letter1942, [see Margaret Sanger Papers]
    - Planned Parenthood News (Chicago)1947-61, [see Margaret Sanger Papers]
    - Planned Parenthood News (PPFA)1952-64, [see Margaret Sanger Papers]
    - Planned Parenthood Review1981-86
    - Planned Parenthood Women's Health Letter1994
    - Planning1954-55, [see Margaret Sanger Papers]
    - Planning Familial (France)1964-66
    - Plexus (Bay Area)1974-85
    - The Population Council Reports on Population/Family Planning1969-74
    - The Population Council Country Profiles1969-72
    - Population Council Studies in Family Planning1963-74
    - Population: Journal of the International Union for the Scientific Investigation of Population Problems1933, [see Margaret Sanger Papers]
    - Population Reports1973-
    - Population: Revue Trimestrielle de L'Institut National D'Etudes Demographiques, 1956, [see Margaret Sanger Papers]
    - Porte Ouverte (Open Door International, Belgium)1934-47
    - Power of Women - Journal of the Power of Woman Collective (London)1974-75
    - The Practitioner (re: birth control, Great Britain)1933
    - Prime Time1971-77
    - Prism Comics1973, [see Homosexuality Collection]
    - Le Probleme Sexuel1933-35, [see Margaret Sanger Papers]
    - Prochoice IDEA (Prochoice Resource Center, Mamaroneck, NY)1994-95
    - Progress1903-09, [located in Flat file]
    - Progressive Woman1971-72
    - Proud Woman1972
    - Provenance: The Journal of the Society of Georgia Archivists1983-94
    - Provincial Freeman1854, [located in Flat files; see also microfilm M12 for 1853-57]
    - Psychology of Women1979-80
    - The PUCE Mongoose1976-77
    - Publication Mensuelle, [see The Bulletin of the American Women of Paris]
    - Purple Rage, undated, [see Homosexuality Collection]
    - The PVPGA (Pioneer Valley People's Gay Alliance) Gayzette1983
  - Q
    - Queen Isabella Journal1890-92, [see Frances Casemant Papers]
    - Quest: A Feminist Quarterly1974-81
  - R
    - Race Relations Reporter1971-73
    - Rain and Thunder1999-2008
    - Raising Cain (Washington (DC) Area Women's Center)1974
    - La Razn Mestiza (San Francisco)1974-80
    - RAT Subterranean News1969-72
    - Rebel Woman1974
    - Reclaiming Newsletter1993
    - The Red Pencil Bulletin1970
    - Red Rag - A Magazine of Women's Liberation (London)1974-78
    - Red Star1971
    - Refractory Girl1974-82
    - Der Regen bagen (Germany)1946
    - Remonstrance1890-1920
    - The Reply1913-14
    - Reproductive Freedom News1992-98
    - Reproductive Rights Newsletter (Chicago)1976-88
    - Research Report (Wellesley College Center for Research on Women)1980-88
    - Response
    - Revista Pan America (Honduras)1946-51
    - The Revolution1868-70, [see also microfilm M12 for 1868-71]
    - Rites - for lesbian and gay liberation1985-86
    - Room of One's Own - A Space for Women's Writing1975-93
    - Roshni (India) - Journal of the All India Women's Conference1948-60
    - Roshi Bulletin1962-64
  - S
    - Saheli: the first four years1985
    - St. Joan's International Alliance Bulletin (U.S.)1976-95, [see also The Catholic Citizen]
    - Samya SHAKTI: A Journal of Women's Studies1984
    - SANEnews: a national newsletter on battered women1978-87
    - Sappho's Isle: The Tri-State Lesbian Newspaper (New York City)1991-95
    - The Saturday Visitor1848-54, [see microfilm M9]
    - SCW News (Southern California)1979-80
    - Scribner's Monthly1877-98
    - The Second Wave1971-75
    - Sensor (Santa Monica, CA)1978-79
    - Sexology1954-1956, [see Margaret Sanger Papers]
    - SHE1973-79
    - Shrew1971-73
    - The Sibyl1856-64, [see microfilm M32]
    - Sibyl-Child: a women's arts and culture journal1977-78
    - Sigma Delta Epsilon News (Graduate Women in Science)1935-79
    - Sigma Delta Epsilon Newsletter (Graduate Women in Science)1969-79
    - Signs: Journal of Women in Culture and Society1989-
    - Sing Heavenly Muse1983-97
    - Sinister Wisdom1976-1998
    - Siren - a liberation newsletter of anarchofeminism1971-72
    - Sister (Los Angeles)1973-79
    - Sister - New Haven Women's Liberation1974-79
    - Sister Advocate (Oklahoma City)1977-80
    - Sister Courage1975-78
    - Sister Source - A Midwest Lesbian / Feminist Newsletter1981-82
    - Sister to Sister - Newsletter of the Women of Color Resource Center, 2003-2008
    - Sisters (Los Angeles Women's Center)1972-79
    - Sisters (San Francisco)1971-75
    - Sisters United (Kansas)1981-83
    - Six Point Group Newsletter1960-76
    - Skip Two Periods (Roanoke, VA)1983-84
    - Snake Power - A Journal of Contemporary Female Shamanism1989
    - Social Welfare (India)1966-69
    - The Socialist Woman1907
    - Sojourner1975-2002
    - The Some Times1977
    - Something About the Women (Manhattan, KS)1981
    - Something Else1970
    - So's Your Old Lady (Minneapolis)1974-77
    - The Source1973-74
    - Sourceline: Alaska's Only Feminist Newspaper1976, 1978
    - Southern Association of Women Historians1992-96
    - Southern Feminist1985-86
    - Soviet Woman1900-83
    - Speaking of Women, [see Women Speaking]
    - Spare Rib (London)1972-92
    - Speak Out - A Feminist Journal (Albany, NY)1974-78
    - Special Issues on Women:
      - A.J.S., Jan. 1973
      - The Atlantic, Mar 1970
      - Bahai Asian Journal, Dec 1981
      - Black Enterprise Aug 1991
      - College University Business Feb 1970
      - CommentaryOct 1981
      - Convergence Feb/Mar 1974
      - Daedalus Fall 1987
      - Design and Environment Spring 1974
      - Dialogue Summer 1971
      - Dimension Jun 1975
      - Edcentric Nov 1974
      - Engineer Feb 1976
      - Esquire Jul 1973
      - Fifth Estate Mar 1971
      - First Issue undated
      - Freedom SocialistFall 1978
      - Globe Magazine Mar 1974
      - Guardian Mar 1977
      - Impact of Science on Society Jul/Aug ?
      - International Socialist Review1970
      - Journal of Social Issues1983
      - Journal of Social Philosophy1984
      - Life1976
      - MademoiselleFeb 1975
      - Maine Times18 Jun 1971
      - Margins Aug 1975
      - The Massachusetts Review1972
      - Mother Jones April 1980
      - Motive Mar/Apr 1969
      - National Lampoon Jan 1971
      - New World OutlookApr 1971
      - New YorkApr 1977
      - New York Times Magazine 24 Nov 1996
      - Nickel Review May 1970
      - Nuclear Times May 1983
      - People (International Planned Parenthood Association) Mar 1980
      - Political Affairs Mar 1971
      - Quicksilver Times Oct 1969
      - Radical America Feb 1970, May/Jun 1980
      - Radical Teacher1977
      - Radical Therapist1970-1975
      - The Real Paper Mar 1977
      - Red Papers1970
      - The Review of Radical Political Economics1972-1976
      - Saint AnthonyMar 1971
      - Scene Fall 1975
      - Socialist Monthly Changes Apr 1983
      - Socialist Woman Jan/Feb 1971
      - The Spark Feb 1972
      - Spin Nov 1997
      - Synergy Dec 1969
      - Southern Exposure1977
      - Time1972-1976
      - Trans Action Nov/Dec 1970
      - Ubyssey, The Feb. 1971
    - Spectre - Paper of Revolutionary Lesbians1971-72
    - Spinning Off1978-80
    - The Spokeswoman1970-81
    - Sportswoman1973-77
    - Springfield Women's Center Newsletter1973-74
    - The Standard1895-1901, [see Flat file]
    - Status of Women News/La Revue Satut de la Femme (National Action Committee onthe Status of Women, Toronto)1976-85
    - Stiletto1900
    - Stri Dharma1931-36
    - Studio Feminist Alliance, [see Ms. On Scene Newsletter]
    - Suffrage News (New Zealand)1992-93
    - The Suffragette1913-21
    - Suffragist1913-21
  - T
    - Tabs1977-81
    - Tacon (Puerto Rico)1975
    - Tell - a - Woman (Philadelphia)1972-75
    - Les Tetes de Pioche - Journal Des Femmes (Quebec)1976-77
    - Themis1979-80
    - The Thesmophoria1982-86
    - Thirteenth Moon1975-83
    - Through the Looking Glass (Seattle)1971-1977
    - Tightwire (Kingston, Ont.)1976
    - The Time and Talents News1900-19
    - Toads1975
    - Today's Woman1979
    - Today: YWCA of India 1970-1979
    - Tooth and Nail (Bay Area)1969-70
    - Together (University of California at Los Angeles)1979
    - La Tortuga (Peru)1982-83
    - Tradeswomen - Magazine for Women in Blue-collar Work1983
    - Tribad (New York City)1977
    - The Tribune (International Women's Year UN Decade for Women)1976-99
    - Triple Jeopardy1970-75
    - Trivia - A Journal of Ideas1982-87
    - Trouble and Strife1983
    - The True Republic1891-92, [see Frances Casemant Papers]
  - U
    - The Udder Side1973
    - The Una1853-55, [see Neilson microfilm 124]
    - Unicorn1980
    - Union Wage1971-82
    - United Association of Women News Sheet1956-73
    - University of Michigan Papers in Women's Studies1974-78
    - Up from Under1970-72
    - US: United Sisters1973-74
  - V
    - Valley Voice
    - Valley Women's Studies Journal1973
    - The Valley Women's Voice1979-95
    - Vanessa and Iris: A Journal for Young Feminists (Brookline High School, Massachusetts)1983-85
    - Velvet Fist1970-71
    - Velvet Glove1971
    - Veteran Feminists of America
    - Vigilance1912-14
    - Vindicacion Feminista (Spain)1976
    - Visibilities1988-91
    - Vital Signs: News from the NBWHP (National Black Women's Health Project)1990-1992
    - Viva: The International Magazine for Women1976-78
    - Viva (Nairobi)1975-82
    - The Vocal Majority1971
    - Vogue1950-2000
    - Voice of Industry1845-46, [see Neilson microfilm 108]
    - Voice of the Women's Liberation Movement1968-69
    - Voice of Women, USA1961-62
    - The Vote1909-29
    - Votes for Women1907-14
    - Vox Medica (Germany)1920, [see Margaret Sanger Papers]
    - Vox Studentium: The International Student Magazine1927, [see Margaret Sanger Papers]
    - Vrouwen1938
    - Vu1938
  - W
    - W.E.B. (Wimmin of the Earth Bonding) Newsletter (Grand Rapids, MI)1982-83
    - Washington Memo (Planned Parenthood Federation of America)1982-83
    - Washington Newsletter for Women1958
    - Washington Woman1980
    - Washington Women's Representative1975-81
    - We Ain't Got It Easy But...We Got It!1975-76
    - We Have Seen You There [1970s?]
    - WEAL (Women's Equity Action League) National Newsletter1970-87
    - Webspinner1983-84
    - The Weekly Visitor and Ladies Museum1817-19
    - Die Welt Der Frau1952
    - Weal (Washington Report)1971-90
    - The Western Woman Voter1911-13, [see also microfilm M6]
    - What It Is?1976
    - White House News on Women1979-80
    - Whole Woman1973-74
    - WHOM (Women Historians of the Midwest) Newsletter1987-96
    - Wicce1975, [see Homosexuality Collection]
    - Widening Horizons1932-75
    - Wild Women Sports (Western Massachusetts)1990-91
    - WIN (Women's International Network News)1975-
    - Win Magazine1970-75
    - The Window1976
    - Wires: Women's Liberation Movement Newsletter1979
    - WOAR (Women Organized Against Rape) Path1974-78
    - Woman1988
    - The Woman with Woman's Digest1940-42
    - Woman (Women's Center of Dallas)1978-80
    - Woman (Kalamazoo, MI)1973
    - The Woman (National Council of Women of the Republic of Korea)1966-70
    - The Woman Activist1970-78
    - Woman Art1976-78
    - The Woman Citizen1917-18
    - Woman's Monthly Vol.6 No.2 October 1997
    - WomaNews (New York City)1981-88
    - Woman of Power1984-95
    - The Woman Patriot1919-24, [see microfilm M37]
    - Woman Power1971-79
    - The Woman Rebel1914, [see Margaret Sanger Papers]
    - Woman Space1976-82
    - Woman Speak (Australia)1993
    - Woman Spirit1974-84
    - Woman Suffrage1887, [see Frances Casemant Papers]
    - Woman Tide1980-85
    - Woman Time1977
    - Woman to Woman1979-89
    - Woman Voter1912-16, [see also microfilm M5 for 1910-17]
    - Woman's Advocate1869
    - Woman's Art Journal1980-91
    - Woman's Chronicle1889, [see Frances Casemant Papers]
    - Woman's Column1892-1903
    - The Woman's Era1894-97, [see Neilson microfilm 126]
    - Woman's Home Companion1915-1957
    - Woman's Journal1870-1917, [see also microfilm M23 for 1870-1913, reels 2-6 missing 1/30/02]
    - Woman's Journal (Hingham, MA)1985
    - Woman's Journal (Northampton, MA)1971-72
    - Woman's National Magazine1917
    - The Woman's Newspaper (New Jersey)1983-84
    - Woman's Newspaper of Princeton1982-86
    - The Womans Press (YWCA)1919-52, [see also YWCA Interchange]
    - Woman's Progressive Weekly1913
    - Woman's Protest1912-18, [see also microfilm M7]
    - The Woman's Pulpit1952-91
    - Woman's Recorder1892, [see Frances Casemant Papers]
    - The Woman's Standard1886-1911, [see microfilm M11]
    - A Woman's Touch1982
    - The Woman's Tribune1889-90, 1902,1908, [see also Frances Casement Papers]
    - Woman's Voice1970
    - Woman's Welfare1904
    - Woman's Work (Women's Missionary Society of the Presbyterian Church)1886-94
    - Woman's World (London)1888-90 (microfilm 479)
    - Woman's World (New York)1971-72
    - Woman's World and Jenness Miller monthly1898, [see Flat File]
    - Womanspace News1986, [see Homosexuality Collection]
    - Women 2000, 1988-94, [see also Women News]
    - Women: A Berkshire Feminist News Journal1974-77
    - Women: Berkshire Women's Liberation Newsletter1972-74
    - Women: A Journal of Liberation (Baltimore)1969-83
    - Women - To By Of For & About1970
    - Women Against Pornography1982-87
    - Women Against Sexist Violence (in Pornography and Media)1981
    - Women Against Violence (in Pornography and Media News Page)1977-82
    - Women and Art1971-72
    - Women and Environments International Newsletter1978-86
    - Women and Film1972-75
    - Women and History1982-87
    - Women and Language News1976-79
    - Women and Revolution1971-86
    - Women and Work1973-82
    - Women Are Human1973-79
    - Women Artists News1978-85
    - Women as Women as Women: Kansas City Women's Liberation Union Newsletter,1974-77
    - Women at Work (National Commission on Working Women)1981-82
    - Women Can (Vancouver)1974?
    - Women Centered News (Albany, NY)1982-84
    - Women for Peace Bulletin (Chicago)1980-84
    - Women Healing1981
    - Women Historians of the Midwest Newsletter, [see WHOM Newsletter]
    - Women in Action1947-80
    - Women in Education1981-85
    - Women in Hartford1986-89
    - Women in Midstream1975-76
    - Women in Music1935-40
    - Women in Struggle1973-75
    - Women in the Arts Bulletin1977-81
    - Women in the Work Force 1988-1989
    - Women in the World1975-76
    - Women Lawyer's Journal1949-67
    - Women Make Movies Newsletter1980-81
    - Women New York1978-79
    - Women News (UN Office at Vienna)1989-91, [see also Women 2000]
    - Women of China1958-65
    - Women of the Whole World1951-91
    - Women on the March (Women's Department of the All India Congress Committee,New Dehli)1961-69
    - Women Office Workers Newsletter1976-77
    - Women Space (Cleveland, OH)1976
    - Women Speaking1951-82
    - Women Today (formerly African Women)1954-81